[{"answer": " Hey, Ingrid.  How was your day", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 15, "question": "", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " It was tiring!  I had science labs all day", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Hey, Ingrid.  How was your day", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " That sucks.  How come youre home so late", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 17, "question": " It was tiring!  I had science labs all day", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Oh, I had to wait forever for the bus.  It was 30 minutes late", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 18, "question": " That sucks.  How come youre home so late", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " What time did you leave school", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Oh, I had to wait forever for the bus.  It was 30 minutes late", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": "Four oclock", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 20, "question": " What time did you leave school", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " What!?  That was two hours ago.  It took you that long to get home", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 21, "question": "Four oclock", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Yep.  The bus was late and then it broke down and I had to wait another 4", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 22, "question": " What!?  That was two hours ago.  It took you that long to get home", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Thats terrible!  Im sorry to hear that", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Yep.  The bus was late and then it broke down and I had to wait another 4", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Thanks.  Im seriously considering buying a car.  It would be much mor", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Thats terrible!  Im sorry to hear that", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Yeah, I think it would be", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Thanks.  Im seriously considering buying a car.  It would be much mor", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Do I need to get a U.S. drivers license", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Yeah, I think it would be", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " You know Im not sure.  Lets look online", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Do I need to get a U.S. drivers license", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " OK.  Thanks", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 37, "question": " You know Im not sure.  Lets look online", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " OK, the schools webpage for international students says that you dont have t", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 38, "question": " OK.  Thanks", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Why", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 42, "question": " OK, the schools webpage for international students says that you dont have t", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": "Well, it says that it will be easier to get car insurance with one and that its les", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Why", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Does it say what I need to do to get a U.S. license", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 47, "question": "Well, it says that it will be easier to get car insurance with one and that its les", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " No.  It tells us to look at the DMVs website.  Lets look at that.  OK.  So it say", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Does it say what I need to do to get a U.S. license", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " All right.  I should have all of those documents", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 53, "question": " No.  It tells us to look at the DMVs website.  Lets look at that.  OK.  So it say", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " So, you just bring those documents to the DMV and you fill out an application", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 54, "question": " All right.  I should have all of those documents", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " What?  I have to take a written and a driving test?  Why", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 58, "question": " So, you just bring those documents to the DMV and you fill out an application", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Probably cause the driving rules are so different here in the U.S. than in othe", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 59, "question": " What?  I have to take a written and a driving test?  Why", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Whats the written test like?  Is it hard", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Probably cause the driving rules are so different here in the U.S. than in othe", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Not really.  You can get a little book from the DMV, which you can study for th", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Whats the written test like?  Is it hard", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " Whats on it", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Not really.  You can get a little book from the DMV, which you can study for th", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " It asks you questions about signs and different driving rules that your", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Whats on it", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " What about the driving test?  Is that hard", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 75, "question": " It asks you questions about signs and different driving rules that your", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Since you already know how to drive, it should be easy.  You just drive in a ca", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 76, "question": " What about the driving test?  Is that hard", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " I hope not.  I would hate to fail!  Ill have to study that book you were talkin", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Since you already know how to drive, it should be easy.  You just drive in a ca", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " You definitely should.  I took the test without studying when I was 16 and ", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 85, "question": " I hope not.  I would hate to fail!  Ill have to study that book you were talkin", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Ill definitely study then", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 88, "question": " You definitely should.  I took the test without studying when I was 16 and ", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " Do you want to make an appointment online for the tests now", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 89, "question": " Ill definitely study then", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " No, not right now.  Let me think a little more about it first and look for a car", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Do you want to make an appointment online for the tests now", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "05-03", "aSentId": 91, "question": " No, not right now.  Let me think a little more about it first and look for a car", "qSentId": 90}]
